▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓| En Français plus bas |▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓			▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓	  ENGLISH	▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓			▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓|      CuttyCupcakes      |▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓

A font made by Jellyka Nerevan, From CuttyFruty
Jellyka@gmail.com

For more fonts or information about me, please, 
go to http://www.cuttyfruty.com


▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒

	All my fonts, including this one, are free for a personal use.
	If you want to do something commercial it, a simple donation is demanded. Have more informations
	on my website: www.cuttyfruty.com 

▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒

Find me on Cuttyfruty
http://www.cuttyfruty.com/enhtml/
Find me on deviantart
http://jellyka.deviantart.com


▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓| F.A.Q: |▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓

What is commercial ?

	Everything sold.
	Examples: T-shirts, logos, Posters, Album or book cover, etc.

What is personnal ?

	Anything staying on the internet as a web objet is considered as a personnal work.
	Examples: Banners, userbars, avatars, website skins, blogs, etc.
	And everybody can do scrapbooking with my font. 
	( But cannot printed letters and sell them )
	Homeworks, party invitations or other things like that are also considered as personnal stuff.

I am not sure if it's commercial or not, what can I do ?

	Just e-mail be at Jellyka@gmail.com , I will probably respond to you within one week.

I want to do something commercial with your font, can I buy it ?

	Yes. You just have to do a donation through paypal. You choose how much you give me, it really
	depends on you. It depends on what you think is important (like, how much my work worth, how big
	the project you wanna do is big, how much you are willing to give etc.)

I don't have a paypal account, but I want to do something commercial with your font !!
	A paypal account is not required to do a donation. You can use your credit card, or, where it is
	possible, your bank account. Have more informations on my website, CuttyFruty.com. 

And... Once I've done a donation, where's the proof I bought it ?
	Paypal always remembers what did happen on an account. So, the fact you did send me money
	and how much you gave will be on paypal, and on your bank's/credit card history. However,
	it protects me too, because I can prove that someone hasn't paid ;-)

Oh... And I really can do something commercial after that ?
	Yes, you have the right to do whatever you want with one of my fonts. But be aware that it is 
	one separate donation per font you want !

How much should I donate ?
	It's up to you ! There's no minimum, and no maximum, and no 'average donations' either.

If I e-mail you, will you give me a better indication about how much I should give ?
	Absolutely not. I'll answer exactly the same thing !




▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓			▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓	 FRANÇAIS	▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓			▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓|     CuttyCupcakes        |▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓

Une police d'écriture créée par Jellyka Nerevan, CuttyFruty.
Jellyka@gmail.com

Pour plus de polices ou d'informations à propos de moi, s'il vous plait,
vous rendre sur http://www.cuttyfruty.com



▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒

	Toutes mes polices, incluant celle-ci, sont Gatuites pour un usage personnel.
	Pour une utilisation commerciale, je demande simplement un don via paypal.

▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒▒

Trouvez-moi sur CuttyFruty
http://www.cuttyfruty.com/html
Trouvez-moi sur deviantart
http://jellyka.deviantart.com


▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓| F.A.Q: |▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓

Qu'est-ce qui est commercial ?

	Tout ce qui est vendu.
	Exemples: T-shirts, logos, Posters, Pochette d'album, Couverture de livre, etc.

Qu'est-ce qui est personnel ?

	Tout objet web, qui reste et restera sur le net, est considéré comme personnel.
	Exemples: Bannières, userbars, avatars, kits graphiques, blogs, etc.
	Aussi, tout le monde peut faire du Scrapbooking avec mes fonts. 
	( Mais vous ne pouvez pas imprimer des lettres et les vendre, par exemple. )
	Les devoirs, cartons d'invitations et les autres choses dans le genre sont considérées comme
	étant personnelles.

Je suis pas certain(e) si ce que je m'apprête à faire est commercial ou non, que faire ?

	Écrivez moi un e-mail à Jellyka@gmail.com , Je devrais être en mesure de vous répondre à 
	l'intérieur d'une semaine.

Je veux faire quelque chose de commercial avec cette police, puis-je l'acheter ?

	Oui. Pour une utilisation commerciale, je demande un don via paypal. Vous choisissez combien 
	vous me donnez, ça ne relève que de votre choix. 

Mais je n'ai pas de compte paypal ?!

	Ce n'est pas grave ! Pour faire un don, vous pouvez utiliser une carte de crédit ou encore,
	dans les établissements où c'est admis, faire un virement depuis votre compte bancaire. 
	pour plus d'informations, rendez-vous sur mon site web, cuttyfruty.com

Et où est la preuve que je l'ai achetée ?
	
	Paypal se souvient de tout ce qui se passe sur un compte, et le virement sera inscrit sur
	votre relevé bancaire ou de carte de crédit. De plus, cela me protège aussi, car en
	recevant certaines informations telles que le montant du don et le nom, je peux vérifier
	si quelqu'un a bel et bien payé.

Donc... Après avec fait un don, je peux faire quelque chose de commercial ?

	Oui, vous avez ensuite le droit de faire ce que bon vous semble avec l'une de mes polices
	d'écriture. cependant, notez bien que c'est un don par police que vous souhaitez utiliser !

Combien devrais-je donner ?
	Il n'y a aucun prix fixe, ni aucun prix minimum. Vous êtes le seul à décider combien vous
	donnez.

Me donneras-tu un prix plus précis si je te contacte ?
	Non. Je répondrai exactement la même chose !


▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓
Jellyka Nerevan
CuttyFruty.com
Jellyka@gmail.com
22/06/2010